[Music]
hey guys pastor myers here welcome to
our second episode of i got a question
thank you guys for sending in your
questions we are getting a bunch of them
and i promise you we will get to them
today's episode we're going to be
covering two questions
question number one is this
do you believe satan will impersonate
jesus before
or after the close of probation for the
world
this question deals with the idea that
satan will pretend to be christ
and it is considered the last deception
before
jesus returns to this earth to claim his
own
um the answer to this question is really
very simple
i want you to think of it like this if
the purpose of satan is
to deceive the very elect
that would mean that probation must
still be open
in order for people to be able to change
their minds in order for people to be
deceived
when satan appears as jesus
he is doing so with the hopes
of changing people's minds of of leading
them to
to believe something different than what
they believed before
so when satan appears probation is still
open
right people can still choose whether
they're going to accept
this counterfeit as the messiah or
reject him as the messiah
if satan were to appear after probation
closes
everybody's mind is already made up his
deception
wouldn't be deception at all it wouldn't
mean anything
so it is clear that when he appears
uh it is while probation is still open
to the world and by the way probation
only closes
once right there's not a close of
probation for the church and the close
of pervasion for the world
that is another question that we'll
probably get into it another time
but probation closes when michael stands
up
and michael stands up only once
question number two should a christian
have a gun to protect themselves in
these crazy times
a person goes on to say i don't have a
gun i've never touched one
i don't believe in killing anybody but i
do believe that we have the right to
protect ourselves to the best
of our ability so to answer that
question i'm going to say this
i'm going to rephrase that does a
christian have a right to bear arms and
i'm going to answer that we
already bear arms
we can use these as weapons right the
question to me is not about
guns although we have a second amendment
right you know in america that you know
it is legal to bear arms
everybody knows that but i think the
question the real
question is do we have a right to defend
ourselves yeah guns kill uh
baseball bats can kill knives can kill
hands can kill
so i believe that the bottom line is
that
you have a right to defend yourself to
defend your family
if someone breaks into your home and
they are harming your
children you are not going to stand
by and watch them harm your children
right
um you're going to call the police
you're going to do what you need to do
but in the meantime
you're not going to stand there and
allow them to harm your children
right if i'm in a situation i'm doing
whatever i can to restrain that person
as best i can
and what that looks like i can't tell
you i just hope i will never be in that
situation
but i can tell you that you do have a
right to protect yourself uh to protect
your family
you know it's a challenging question for
a lot of people but i i will say this
is it is not a sin to have a gun
any more than it is a sin to have a
knife
baseball bat
or a sin to have arms that can be
considered deadly weapons right
hands that can be considered deadly
weapons you have a right to defend
yourself
and defend yourself and defend your
family
and pray that you never find yourself in
a situation like that
so i hope that answers your question and
i will see you on the next episode
of i got a question so remember if you
have a question
go ahead and text 866
three five two six two or
eight six six god lamb and uh make sure
to follow me on instagram at ivory myers
i will see you in our next episode
you